[{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bfe","Question":"Is there a way that I can re-upload my assignment to my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Assignments","RT_reference":"1131854","Answer":"You can upload your assignment again only if the instructor has made multiple attempts available to the students.<br>If you do not have options for multiple attempts, please contact your instructor. <br>Your instructor can either clear your first attempt or change the settings","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bff","Question":"How can I subscribe to my team discussion board? I can't see the subscription button.","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1112663","Answer":"To have \"Subscribe\" feature for Discussion Board, please follow the steps below.<br><br>- Create a Discussion Board menu in the Content Area.Click the Discussion Board<br>- Create a new discussion forum by clicking the + Forum button at the top left of the window <br>- Name the discussion forum<br>- Click \"Allow members to subscribe to forum\" ( By default, Blackboard has the \"Do not allow subscriptions.\")","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342c00","Question":"Why can't my professor find me in the course that I am enrolled? My professor tried to add me to the course manually but she failed to find me.","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1131989","Answer":"It is possible that instructors are not familiar with adding users to the course site; When instructors add users to the course site, they type user's net ID including uic.edu, which can lead to fail add yours to the course site. Another reason is that instructors click 'Browse' when attepmting to search for the user's net ID.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be2","Question":"Do you provide media conversion services to students?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1061824","Answer":"We only provide faculty and Staff support. Media conversion is strictly for academic use. If a course demands certain material that requires the conversion, we will be more than happy to convert the content to a DVDprovided to us. However, if the VHS tapes contain personal content, we will unfortunately not be able to convert them for the student.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be5","Question":"How can my students view feedback for each individual question?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1224293","Answer":"1.  Student enters the 'My Grades' tool and clicks the title of the test to view the attempt details. If they were to click the blue buBlackboardle next to the score, they will only see the overall feedback. <br>2.  In the 'View Attempts' page, the student will see their grade. To view the feedback, they will need to click their grade. <br>3.  Here students will see feedback for individual responses.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be6","Question":"What do I do if I am unable to view my instructor's lecture on Sharestream?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1213921","Answer":"For trouble shooting follow these steps in order: <br>1.  Try accessing the videos directly from within the units<br>2.  Make sure your're not in a private session ( private browsing, incognito mode etc.)  and that cookies are enabled for your browser<br>3.  Clear your browsers cache<br>4.  Change your browser ( Google Chrome is recommended)  If you are using Google Chrome, make sure it is up-to-date and if so, please try accessing the videos with Mozilla Firefox","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be7","Question":"Why does Copying Group Discussion Forums Show Users from Other Groups?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1179969","Answer":"This is a known bug. A fix is scheduled for a future release, but in the meantime, the following workaround steps are available: <br><br>1.  Go to Control Panel > Users and Groups > Groups<br>2.  Hover over the group( s)  that needs to be fixed<br>3.  Click the menu item and then Edit<br>4.  When the window opens click Submit ( no need to make any changes here)","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be8","Question":"Why am I unable to upload content to my course? I see the error message: 'Failed File system entry not readable: /courses/comm2-con'","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1177860","Answer":"This problem has been observed in older work-sites. This is due to the fact that Content System permissions were retroactively added. To correct the permissions, do the following:<br>- Navigate to \"COURSEmongo_id > Content System > COURSEmongo_id\"<br>- Click the drop down arrow next to 'Course Content: COURSEmongo_id' > Permissions<br>- Select Specific Users<br>- Enter user's netid in the relevant field<br>- Select 'Read, Write, Remove, Manage'<br>- Submit change","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be9","Question":"How do I upload grades from the iclicker app ( on my laptop)  to blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1208533","Answer":"When you click \"Sync Scores\", i>clicker will communicate with your LMS to upload i>clicker polling data into your LMS gradebook. If you have not saved your LMS credentials, you will be prompted to enter your credentials.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bea","Question":"What are the steps to be followed if the ACCC password gets expired for an user ?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1224537","Answer":"If you remember your expired password, you can still use it to log in at password.uic.edu to create a new password ( as long as your accounts have not been deleted) . You can also call the accounts department for assistance at ( 312)  413-0003.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342beb","Question":"Why are group assignment not displaying to students after the due date was updated?","Category":"Blackboard - Groups","RT_reference":"1174683","Answer":"It would seem that the best practice for changing due dates is one of the following: - <br>Make assignment unavailable, update due date and then, make the assignment available again - Delete the assignment and create a new one with the update due date","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bec","Question":"Why do students see other groups listed in their 'My Grades'?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1175304","Answer":"This is a known bug. Students enrolled in group a specifc group ( usually group 1)  see columns for all the groups<br>in<br>their gradebooks. They only<br>see<br>grades that are entered for them, but they also see a bunch of<br>empty columns. They DO NOT see any other groups' grades, however.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bee","Question":"How can I give a student marked as 'unavailable' access to my course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1174227","Answer":"You need to change the students availability in the course. <br>1.  Go to Users and Groups<br>2.  Users<br>3.  STUDENT_NAME and click on the chevron that appears to the right of the unavailable student's Name<br>4.  Click on \"Change user's availability in the course\" to change their availability","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bef","Question":"Why can't I see a column in the Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1213364","Answer":"The column may be hidden. To unhide a column:<br>1.  Go to to top action bar click MANAGE <br>2.  Select column organization<br>3.  Find the column you want to see and select it and click on show/hide button on the top.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf0","Question":"Why can't I save my answers after I finished the exam?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1184040","Answer":"The error message presented in this ticket implies that the student accidentally logged out of shiboleth without knowing so. This can be done in mulitple ways. If you have blackboard open in 1 tab and another tab using gmail with both personal and uic accounts and you log out of 1 of the gmail accounts, it logs you out of both, while at the same time logging you out of your shiboleth blackboard site. When you try to do something in the blackboard site the error message appears, you simply have to restart your browser and log back into shiboleth.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf1","Question":"Can I call in to Blackboard Collaborate with my phone?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1159464","Answer":"Yes, you are still able to call in if the teleconferencing option is turned on for the room. To do so, the instructor of the course must toggle the 'Use built-in' option under 'Teleconferencing Options' for the room/session in question. It is turned off by default","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf2","Question":"How do I solve the 'Roster File Not Found' error in iClicker?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1109021","Answer":"Ignore for a moment. Then click on gradebook, and click the sync button. You get that error the first time only because you have not yet synced. It assumes that you have configured settings for the gradebook tab, and configured to sync with Blackboard.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf3","Question":"Why can't I see the courses I am enrolled in?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1071668","Answer":"The possible reason why you are not able to view your course sites is that your instructor has not made the course available to the students yet. Please contact the instructor and let them know that you are not available to view the course site.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf4","Question":"How can I delete all of the old content that was copied from a previous course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1085126","Answer":"To delete some or all of the old content from the previous course site, please follow the steps below.<br><br>- Log in to the current course site.<br>- Under Course Management, click \"Packages and Utilities\" and click \" Bulk Delete.\"<br>- Select boxes next to content materials that you intent to delete ( e.g., announcement and Assignments) .<br>- Under Confirmation, type \"Delete.\"<br>- Click Submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf5","Question":"How can I change my course name?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1071609","Answer":"To change your course title, please follow the steps below.<br><br>- Log in to your course site.<br>- Under Course Management, click Customization<br>- Click Properties.<br>- Change the course title in the Course Name.<br>- Click Submit button.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf6","Question":"Why do I see a blank page when I access my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1056180","Answer":"There are two possibilities of this issue either1)  when there is no content under a course menu ( e.g., Announcement) , or 2)  when course materials are stored under course tools in which are only visible to the instructors. <br><br>If it is the first case, add the content under the course menu. Then, your students will be able to view the content.<br><br>If it is the second case, the course materials have to be moved to the content area in which is visible to students. To move the content materials, please contact us at 312-996-9824.  We will walk you through the steps over the phone.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf8","Question":"Why am I still seeing the course I dropped?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1056848","Answer":"Usually, after the semester, you will automatically no longer view your old course site. If you are still seeing the old course site, please let us know the course title that you intend to remove from your Blackboard site. We will remove you from the old course site on our end.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf9","Question":"How can an instructor access their course as a student?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1056318","Answer":"Using Student Preview mode allows you to view course site as a student's view, take tests, submit assignments and view your grades. <br><br>To enter Student Preview, please follow the steps below.<br><br>To view the course as a student,<br><br>- Log in to your course site.<br>- Make sure that the Edit Mode is on at the top right of the course site. <br>- In the left side of Edit mode, click Student Preview button ( circle arrows) .<br>- You will be able to view the course content as a student.<br>- Check \"Delete the preview user and all data<br>- Click Continue.<br><br>To take tests or submit assignments <br><br>- Follow the steps above<br>- When exiting Student Preview, click \"Keep the preview user and all data.\"<br>- Click Continue. <br>- Your preview user account is created and you now will be able to take tests or submit assignments.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bfa","Question":"Why do I get an error message when accessing Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1097259","Answer":"Error message can be fixed by clearing caches and cookies in your Internet browser. Please log out your blackboard site and clear the caches and cookies. Here is a link to how to clear caches and cookies: http://www.refreshyourcache.com/en/home/","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bfb","Question":"Is there a way to see whether or not a student has logged onto a particular blackboard site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1078039","Answer":"Yes, you can track student's activity such as attendance in your Blackboard site by using a Course Report Tool. <br><br>Here are the steps for generating course reports.<br><br>1.  On the control panel, click \"Evaluation\" and select \"Couse reports.\"<br>2.  Select the list of information that you need ( e.g., All User Activity Inside Content Areas) .<br>3.  Select \"Run\".<br>4.  Select \"a Start and End date\" and click \"Submit\"<br><br>For your reference, here is a link with a detailed instruction which shows how to generate course reports: https://help.blackboard.com/enus/Learn/9.1_SP_10_and_SP_11/Instructor/040_Student_Course_Experience/Student_Performance/Generating_Course_Reports","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bfc","Question":"Is there a way to edit my post in the Discussion Board?","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1111681","Answer":"You can edit or delete your posts only if the instructor has made these options available to students. <br>If you do not have options \"Edit\" or \"Delete,\" please contact your instructor.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bfd","Question":"How can I use the Weighted Total column in the Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1081594","Answer":"- Go to the Course Management panel and select Grade Center -> Full Grade Center<br>- In the tab select Create Calculated Column -> Weighted Column<br>- Add each category that requires a selected weight ( or individual column) <br>- Assign each category t","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342c01","Question":"Why can't I see a horizontal scroll bar in Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1137280","Answer":"http://accc.uic.edu/service/Blackboard/mac-os-no-horizontal-scroll-bar","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342c02","Question":"Why can't I view course materials after the professor added me as a guest to the course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1141964","Answer":"http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/guest-access","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"5776b1874704e0e83073eaf4","Question":"This is a test question about penguins","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"","Answer":"<p>This is a test answer about <b>penguins</b>.</p><p><ol><li><span style=\"line-height: 1.42857;\">Penguin 1</span><br></li><li><span style=\"line-height: 1.42857;\">Penguin 2</span></li><li><span style=\"line-height: 1.42857;\"><b><i>Penguin 2</i></b><br></span></li></ol></p>","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231@uic.edu","Submitted_by":"skhan231@uic.edu","Created_on":"2016-07-01T18:08:07.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-07-01T18:08:07.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b69","Question":"How do you allow students to access past courses?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1132506","Answer":"There are 2 ways to do it:<br>1)  Make the course available to all the students<br>2)  Make all the students except the one who needs access to the course, unavailable from the course and then make the course available<br>To make the students unavailable from the course, follow the steps in the link: https://www.ndsu.edu/fileadmin/www.its.ndsu.edu/instruct/blackboard/students_unavailable_in_Blackboard9.pdf","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6a","Question":"How do you deploy a test?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1116811","Answer":"1)  First, go into the course and toggle Edit Mode to ON ( Edit mode is present on the top right side inside your course) <br>2)  Click on the Content Area ( on the left pane)  where you wanted to deploy the test<br>3)  From there, click Assessments->Test<br>4)  Select the test you wish to deploy from \"Add an Existing Test\" and click submit<br>5)  You may set any of the optional settings for due date and availalabilty date and once you're done, Click submit.<br><br>Link to the video: https://uofi.box.com/s/e9hai9bt9zhexeppnxaeec6ocm5q72q8","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6b","Question":"How do I enable guest permissions in Blackboard so that guests have access to contents of the course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1143342","Answer":"Follow the steps beow:<br>1)  Go into your course<br>2)  On the left pane, Under \"Control Panel\" go to \"Customization\"<br>3)  Click on \"Guest and Observer Access\"<br>4)  Click Yes on the \" Allow Guests\" radio button<br>5)  Hit the \"Submit\" button at the bottom of the page","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6c","Question":"How can I clear an attempt of a student in Grade center ?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1148294","Answer":"Follow the steps beow:<br>1)  Go into your course<br>2)  On the left pane, Under \"Control Panel\" go to \"Grade Center\"<br>3)  Click on \"Full Grade Center\"<br>4)  Hover your mouse over a particular cell in the required \"Column\" against a particular student. A chevron shoud appear<br>5)  Click on the Chevron and then click \"View Grade Details\"<br>6)  You will taken to a different page. Under \"Attempts\" tab, you will see the option of \"Clear Attempt\" under actions<br><br>You can also refer to the following link: http://du.screenstepslive.com/s/docs/m/7137/l/78380-clear-student-attempt-in-grade-center","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6e","Question":"Which team should you contact regarding lecture centre/rooms and their corresponding facilities ?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1231297","Answer":"You need to contact the \"LETS\" department to get answers to questions regarding Rooms/Lecture Centres. You can contact them by mailing to classrooms@uic.edu or calling at 312-996-2751 ( General Inquiries) , 312-996-4648 ( Urgent Help Line)","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6f","Question":"How do you create a smart view in the Grade Center and deploy it?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"NONE","Answer":"Refer to the below links: <br>http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/smart-views<br>http://library.blackboard.com/ref/36ba3329-e441-488a-93ce-7a55543cc999/Content/Grade%20Center/Creating%20Smart%20Views%20in%20the%20Grade%20Center.htm","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b71","Question":"How do I enable adaptive release option in a blackboard course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"NONE","Answer":"When Adaptive Release option is not seen as a part of Assignment/Item, you need to enable it for the course. Follow the steps below to enable it:<br>1)  Go into the course<br>2)  Under Control Panel click on \"Customization\" <br>3)  Under Tool Availability, Check the required check box for adaptive release <br>4)  Hit the submit button","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b72","Question":"How do you set an extra credit option in tests ?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"NONE","Answer":"Giving Extra credits for tests: <br>https://www.cod.edu/it/blackboard/ExtraCreditTest.htm<br><br>Extra credits in Grade Center:<br>1)  https://coursessupport.gmu.edu/Faculty/index.cfm?audiencename=Faculty&categoryname=Blackboard%20Grade%20Center&datname=How%20to%20Give%20Extra%20Credit%20to%20Students%20in%20the%20Grade%20Center<br>2)  http://www.ju.edu/ctl/Documents/Blackboard_Tutorials/extra_credit_Blackboard9.pdf","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b73","Question":"How do I copy content from one course to another?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1053306","Answer":"1)  Enroll as instructor in destination course<br>2)  Access the Blackboard course you want to copy.<br>3)  On the Control Panel, expand the Packages and Utilities section > Course Copy.<br>4)  Select the option: Copy Course Materials into an Existing Course<br>5)  Click the Browse button to view a list of your courses. In the popup window that appears, select the appropriate course ID from your list of courses and click Submit. The course ID will populate in the Destination Course ID Box.<br>6)  Select the course materials that you want to copy over to the existing course. We recommend Select All.( Unless exceptions are specified) <br>7)  In the File Attachments section, select Copy links and copies of the content. ( if there is .swf select Copy links and copies of the content ( include entire course home folder) )  <br>8)  Click Submit.<br><br>Note: DO NOT select Include Enrollments in the Copy.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b74","Question":"How do I copy a test from one course site to another?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1066375","Answer":"To export a test:<br>1)  Go to the Control Panel > Course Tools > Tests, Surveys, and Pools > Tests. <br>2)  Then click the action link ( the double down arrow)  next to the test you created. <br>3)  From the menu, select Export to Local Computer. <br>4)  Save the exported file to your computer.  It will be a .zip file. Do not make any changes to the zip file.<br><br>5)  In the second course, follow the same path to navigate to the Test manager. <br>7)  Click the Import Test button and find the file on your computer. <br>8)  Once the test has been Imported, you can deploy the test and and set the options.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b75","Question":"Can I backup my course content to my local computer?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1071535","Answer":"To create an Archive or an Export file:<br>1)  Go to the Control Panel and select Packages and Utilities > Export/Archive Course. <br>2)  Select the items you would like to export, then click Submit. <br>3)  When you receive the confirmation email, log back in to your course and go to Export/Archive Course to find your backup file.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b77","Question":"How do I bulk upload students onto my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1083887","Answer":"1)  Receive excel file from instructor in the following format and save as .csv with the following columns:<br>  - Column 1: courseID<br>  - Column 2: valid NetID<br>  - Column 3: Role ( S - Student) <br><br>2)  Go to SysAdmin Panel > Courses<br>3)  Click Enroll Users<br>4)  Browse file<br>5)  Select delimiter type 'Comma'<br>6)  Click Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b78","Question":"How do I remove old courses from my Blackboard homepage?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1084244","Answer":"Go to course site to be removed and then:<br>1)  Control Panel > User and Groups <br>2)  Look up user and click chevron/ action link<br>4)  Select Change user's availiility in course<br>5)  Chenge to 'No'<br>6)  Click Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b79","Question":"After enrolling a new user to my course, I do not see the other users. How do I get them back?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1085612","Answer":"After adding a user to a course, the Search feild is populated with the netID of the user just added. Update to: <br>1)  Search > NetID > Contains<br>2)  Click 'Contains' and slelect 'Not Blank' from drop-down list<br>3)  Click Go","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7a","Question":"Does Blackboard send announcements out without the course being available to students?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1086819","Answer":"Announcements are not visible to students as long as the course is not open to them ( since the said course is not part of their course list) . So the announcement that went out will not be seen by students. <br><br>However, if you selected the check-box next to \"Email Announcement\" the announcement is sent to their UIC email address irrespective of the availability of the course.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7b","Question":"Is there a way to have Blackboard record the student's grade with a penalty if they submit their assignment late?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1095946","Answer":"No. Blackboard does not have an option to do so. There is no selection/ option that supports deduction of points based on the time of submission.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7c","Question":"Why is Blackboard asking me to install or update my Flash player when I try to play iSpring files, even though I have the latest version on my computer?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1097102","Answer":"This happens due to iSpring content present in the course. iSpring content was not copied over properly from the previous course. <br><br>To resolve this, download lecture modules ( iSpring files)  from the previous course into a zip file and uploaded it in the the current course. So the current course will have all the supporting files to run the lecture modules.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b80","Question":"I allowed students to see all responses from the online quiz, after the availability period has expired. Where do they go to see it?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1123074","Answer":"1)  Go to the course's My Grades<br>2)  When students click on the score that they received for the quiz, they will be able to view all responses including submitted answers and correct answers","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b81","Question":"How can I give access to files in Box without users having to log in?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1113389","Answer":"1.  Log into box<br> with UIC netID and password<br>2.  Look up the file you wish to share<br>3.  Click on \"Share\" from the option on the right side of the file name label<br>4.  In the window that pops up under \"Access\" select \"People with the link\" from the drop down list ( Please see attached screenshot) <br><br>The link in the text box is the link that is shared with the other users.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b82","Question":"How do I download discussion board posts in PDF format?","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1142632","Answer":"1.  Log in to your Blackboard Learn course site<br>2.  Click on the navigation button labeled \"Class Discussion Board\"<br>3.  The list of Discussion Forums will open, browse to the forum in question<br>4.  Scroll to the bottom of the page and click on \"Edit Paging\" and enter maximum value of entries, and click Go<br>5.  Place checkmarks in the boxes next to the messages that you wish to print and then press the button labeled \"Collect\"<br>6.  These can be re-ordered based on a number of options including by date, by student etc.<br>7.  Click on Print Preview, and then select Save as PDF under printer options.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b83","Question":"What is the size limit for files uploaded into SafeAssign and Blackboard assignment space?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1268092","Answer":"Upload limit for SafeAssign is 10MB ( text only - PDF, Word)  i.e. videos cannot be uploaded to SafeAssign sections. <br><br>For Blackboard assignments the upload is limited to 1GB enforced by a hard browser and webserver limit. What this means is with a stable internet connection 1GB of data can be uploaded to the assignment space. Large files take time to upload and it could happen that the session times out, which leaves the action incomplete.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b84","Question":"How do I let a student re-submit an assignment?","Category":"Blackboard - Assignments","RT_reference":"1073116","Answer":"First - clear the first attempt, if applicable. To do that, go Grade Center> click the chevron drop down list next to the student's score > View Grade Details. On this page you have a button to clear attempt.<br>Next, locate the assignment, select 'edit' with the chevron drop down menu, go to 'Availability' and make it available until the time agreed upon with student & instructor.<br>Note: If the assignment is still set to allow a 'single attempt', students who submitted will not be able to resubmit. Unfortunately we could not find a way to make the test only available to the individual student, though that is possible with tests.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b85","Question":"Why can't  a student see their course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1061012","Answer":"Most likely, this is because the instructor has not made the course 'available'  to students yet. If it is 'available', go check the User's availability under Control Panel> Users and Groups and verify whether it is set to 'yes' or 'no'. If it is 'no', figure out why ( i.e., check Banner or find out if it is a recurring problem that needs to be escalated)","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b86","Question":"Why don't some students have access to my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1064412","Answer":"It is good to verify which students are having issues seeing the course. Verify that they are enrolled and have 'yes' next to their names in Users and Groups. Log-in as them to see if they have access. Check Banner for enrollment status.<br><br>Note: An instructor might wonder why the number of users does not match the current enrollment number. Users stay set as 'no' after they drop the course- instructors must manually un-enroll users.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b87","Question":"Why is there extra text/weird formatting when I send an Announcement although it looks fine before sending?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1055436","Answer":"If the instructor copied and pasted from Word, that is a known error that sometimes a lot of extra text can end up in the Announcement, even though it looks normal to you before sending. <br><br>We are working to integrate Word into BlackBoard but for now, there are a a few workarounds. <br><br>First option: Instead of using MS Word, try using a basic text editing program such as Notepad ( for PC) , or Textedit ( for Mac) . <br><br>Second option: After copying and pasting the text from MS Word into your new announcement, you can click \"remove formatting\" from the expanded tool bar menu, just above the spell check button. I included a screenshot of the \"remove formatting\" button for your reference. <br><br>Both of these options should resolve the issue.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b88","Question":"Can you remove me from old courses?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1110833","Answer":"Yes, it is possible to remove anyone from any courses in which they do not want to be enrolled.Go to Users> Remove User","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b89","Question":"How do I add a profile picture/avatar?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1070403","Answer":"1.         Click the arrow next to your name in the page header to access the global navigation menu.<br>2.         Click the empty profile image or your existing image to access your profile.<br>3.         On the profiles page, click the Settings & Privacy link.<br>4.         The Settings & Privacy section appears in the right panel. Click Change Picture to upload an image from your computer.<br>5.         Click Save.<br><br>Note: First time users will be prompted to create a \"MyEdu\" account and it is necessary to enroll to add a picture.<br>Instructors will select \"I am employed by\" in the second field and add in UIC and then it will only ask for your e-mail and name. Finally, hit submit.  Students will need to input more info when registering ( i.e. their major, year of study) .","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8a","Question":"How do I edit settings for showing student feedback on a test?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1139838","Answer":"Go to the test> Test Options > scroll down to 'Show Test Results and Feedback to Students'. <br>Setting Feedback Options<br><br>Each rule has two parts: when the feedback will be displayed, and what feedback will be displayed.<br><br>Guide: https://www.cod.edu/it/blackboard/testFeedback.htm","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8b","Question":"How can I import a course template to my new course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1071438","Answer":"ACCC has documention for this:<br>Instructions and template links: http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/importing-exemplary-course-template<br>Video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hpG63_WhUW0&feature=youtu.be&ab_channel=ACCCInstructionalTechnologyLab","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8c","Question":"I want to add a weighted total column. Why is there nothing in \"Select Columns\" section?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1190097","Answer":"This is a known problem and has been reported to BlackBoard. In the meantime, try clearing the cookies or using a different browser ( ex., Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox) .","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8d","Question":"Can I change my name as it appears on Blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1209669","Answer":"As of 2015, this was not possible without changing your name legally with the Registrar's Office. More info from Registrar's Office here: http://registrar.uic.edu/student_records/name_change.html","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8e","Question":"How can I track student views of a content item ( i.e., lecture) ?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1192078","Answer":"Statistics Tracking is the feature for this. The Statistics Tracking is for specific content, like one lecture, and it needs to be turned on in advance to run a report on that one item.  Documentation ( from other institution) : https://helpdesk.uic.edu/accc/Ticket/Attachment/14266292/7852553/Blackboard9%20Statistics%20Tracking.pdf","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b8f","Question":"How do I copy one item ( i.e., folder)  from one of my courses to another?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1209681","Answer":"1.  Ensure the Edit Mode is On<br>2.  Hover and click the chevron to the right side of item/folder name.<br>3.  Select Copy or Move.<br>4.  Use the Destination Course drop down menu to select the course you would like to copy or move the item or folder to.<br>Click the arrow to the right side of item/folder name.<br>5.  Click the Destination Folder Browse button.<br>6.  Select the area in the course you would like to place the item or folder in. You may need to click the Plus Sign ( + button)  to find a folder within a folder.<br>7.  Click submit <br>Example video from inside of a course: https://uofi.box.com/s/3mke8xaxa0h25egc7qu764f6bl2j0uu5","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b90","Question":"How do I print a class roster without photos?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1235360","Answer":"You can download an excel file with user information. It includes a few columns of other information that you can just delete if you don't need it. <br><br>1.  Navigate to Grade Center <br>2.  Click \"Work Offline\" button on right hand side of the screen towards the top. <br>3.  Select Download <br>4.  The Download Grades Screen will appear. In Section 1, under Select Data to Download, click the radio button \"User Information Only.\"<br>5.  Click Submit.<br>6.  The data has been saved. Click the Download button. <br>Example video: https://uofi.box.com/s/yupl4ozp3ng8xvh4omlafj79vx6mfm19","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b91","Question":"Why does 'Check submissions for plagiarism using safe assign' disappear after I save it?","Category":"Blackboard - Assignments","RT_reference":"1235453","Answer":"You can only enable SafeAssign when you make the assignment \"available\". You can still control it's release by setting the dates ( Display After and Display Until)  in the same Availability section.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b92","Question":"How do I move an item into a folder?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1247839","Answer":"Go to the item and hover over it. <br>Click the chevron.<br>Select \"Move\". <br>Select the Destination Folder ( and course, if you want to move it to another one of your course sites) . <br>Select Submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b93","Question":"How do you add content to the Content Area instead of the content system?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1214953","Answer":"Please follow the below mentioned steps to add contents to the navigation menu - <br><br>1.  Click on the course you want to add a link.<br>2.  Click on the PLUS sign on the top left corner of the page and select \"\"Content Area\"\".<br>3.  Type the name (  like Assignments or Course Documents)  you want.<br>4.  Click on \"\"available to users\"\" if you want to make the links available to students.<br>5.  Click on submit.<br>6.  You can drag and drop the links you created by hovering over them.<br><br>For further clarification, please click on the video link that demonstrates the steps you need to take to add contents.<br><br>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=el6fMDAP86w","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b94","Question":"How do you add tools link to the content area in Blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1061548","Answer":"Steps to create a Tool link:<br><br>1.  Go inside the course.<br>2.  Click on the \"+\" sign above the course name.<br>3.  Select the option \"Tool link\"<br>4.  Type the name \"My Grades\" and from the drop down select the option \"My Grades\"<br>5.  Check the option \"Available to the Users\" and hit submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b95","Question":"How does the Portfolios tool work?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1238989","Answer":"Here is the important information you need to know to get started: <br><br>1- Be sure there are \"Portfolio\" and \"Portfolio Homepage\" tool links in your Blackboard course site. \"Portfolio Homepage\" allows students to go back and review their entire portfolio. to You can add both or you can just create a general tool link. See my attached video titled \"Adding Tool Links for Portfolios\" that I made in a demo site, guiding you through the process. <br><br>If you do not add the two links ( or just the general Tools link, which is a link to all tools in BlackBoard) , students will not be able to access it at all. So that is the first step. <br>More info about adding tool links can also be found here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=el6fMDAP86w&ab_channel=ACCCInstructionalTechnologyLab<br><br><br>2- Now that you have access links in your Blackboard course site, you create an Assignment for students to turn something in. The difference from a regular \"Individual submission\" with this process is that you need to select \"Portfolio\" submission under portfolio types.<br><br>In the video \"Portfolio Process\",the first 35 seconds are in a browser where I am working as the instructor. See video: https://uofi.box.com/s/q7txbwxztuttorae68kwcr9urpjauhz9<br><br>I walk you through creating an assignment and selecting \"portfolio submission\" type for your students, so when they go to submit an assignment it is added to their portfolio. 0:35 seconds and on are showing me in another browser as the student, showing me submitting something to my portfolio via the link I just created as an instructor. You can see it is the first time my student account has used Portfolios, so it asks me if I want a tour. You will have the same thing. Each student will need to click \"Create Portfolio\" the first time. <br><br>More information from BlackBoard about Portfolios can be found here: https://en-us.help.blackboard.com/Learn/9.1_2014_04/Instructor/030_Navigation/Portfolios<br><br>And for \"My Portfolios\", which is accessed via the \"Portfolios Homepage\" link,some more info can be found here: https://en-us.help.blackboard.com/Learn/9.1_2014_04/Instructor/030_Navigation/Portfolios/My_Portfolios","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b96","Question":"How to create an item in a Content Area?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1086436","Answer":"1.  Change Edit Mode to ON and access a content area or folder of the desired course.<br>2.  On the action bar, point to Build Content and click Item.<br>3.  On the Create Item page, type a Name.<br>4.  Optionally, type instructions or a description in the Text box.<br>5.  Alternatively, in the Attachments section, click Browse My Computer to upload a file from your computer. The file is saved in Course Files or the Content Collection in the top-level folder. You can also upload a file from the course's storage repository by clicking Browse Content Collection.<br>6.  Select the Options:<br>- Click Yes to Permit Users to View this Content.<br>- Click Yes to Track Number of Views.<br>7.  Select the Display After and Display Until check boxes to enable the date and time selections. Display restrictions do not affect item availability, only when it appears.<br>8.  Click Submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b97","Question":"How do you view all assignment attempts in the Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1172784","Answer":"Instructor can view all the attempts by following the below mentioned steps - <br><br>1.  Go the desired course > Full grade center<br>2.  Select the cell corredponding to the particular student and the assignment > Click on chevron<br>3.  Click on Attempts > View all attempts.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b98","Question":"How can Students see their grades?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1159306","Answer":"Students can view their grades in 3 ways - <br>1.  Log into the account > Click on the Global Navigation Menu > Click on the checkmark icon.<br>2.  Log into the account > On the welcome page, Go to the Tools > My Grades.<br>3.  If the instructor has made Tool link or My Grades link available inside the course then go to the desired course > Tools > My Grades.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b99","Question":"How do you view the feedback given by an instructor on an exam?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1224680","Answer":"In case students cannot view the feedback, ask them to follow the below steps,<br><br>1)  Go to \"My grades\"<br>2)  Click on Exam<br>3)  Click on the score<br>4)  Students will be able to see each question, their answer, right answer and instructors feedback.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9a","Question":"How can I get access to a course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1053715","Answer":"To get access to a course site, the user must be added in the course or the course needs to be made available to the user.<br><br>To add user to a course - <br><br>1.  Under the control panel, select Users and Groups-->Users<br>2.  Click on \"Find Users to Enroll\" located on the top left corner of the Users pane.<br>3.  Enter their NetID or you can browse for it.<br>4.  Select the role you would like to give them.<br>5.  Click on Submit.<br><br>To make course available - <br><br>Please click on the below mentioned link that provides the steps you need to follow to make a course available to the students - <br><br>https://help.blackboard.com/en-us/Learn/9.1_SP_10_and_SP_11/Instructor/040_Student_Course_Experience/Making_a_Course_Available_or_Unavailable<br><br>The link also contains a video named \"Make Course Available\" for further clarification.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9b","Question":"How can I hide courses in My Courses Plus?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1071697","Answer":"It is not possible to hide courses in My Courses Plus tab. There are two ways to hide courses in welcome page - <br><br>1.  Make the course unavailable to the instructor.<br>- OR - <br>1.  Go to Course List Module on the welcome page.<br>2.  In the top right hand corner of that module in the blue bar, click on the icon that looks like a<br>wheel.<br>3.  When the next page opens up, look for the Course Name column. There will be a check in<br>that box next to courses that will appear on your page. Click in that box to get rid of the<br>checkmark. This will then hide the course from the view.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9c","Question":"How do I download all the submitted papers for an assignment?","Category":"Blackboard - Assignments","RT_reference":"1074391","Answer":"Click on the below mentioned link that shows you the steps you need to follow to download the assignment. At the end of the page, below the Grading Downloaded Assignments, you will find a video named \"Downloading Assignments\" of 1min 35s for the same. The video demonstrates the procedure you need to follow to download the assignments.<br><br>https://help.blackboard.com/en-us/Learn/9.1_SP_10_and_SP_11/Instructor/070_Assignments/002_Downloading_Assignments","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9d","Question":"How can I edit my Blackboard notification options?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1074993","Answer":"Please follow the below mentioned steps - <br><br>1)  Log into your account <br>2)  Go to the Notifications DashBoard<br>3)  Edit Notification Settings <br>4)  Bulk Edit Notifications Settings <br>5)  Courses I am taking in <br>6)  Select the a particular course and if you want to receive email notifications for all the courses choose \"All\" <br>7)  Scroll down and you will see three options - 1)  Dashboard, 2)  Email and 3)  Mobile <br>8)  Click on the Email. Customize according to your requirements and you should start receiving the email notifications.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9e","Question":"How can I copy Sharestream videos from one course to another?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1097824","Answer":"1. Quick Enroll in both courses (source and destination)<br>2. Go to the destination course<br>3. Go to Tools > ShareStream Pick n Play<br>4. Once inside, a window appears which prompt you to copy the videos from the existing course > Select Yes.<br>5. Search box will appear > please enter the entire course id in the search box > select the course.<br>6. Once you have selected the highlighted course, you will see all the videos on the new fall site.<br>","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b9f","Question":"Why am I unable to print class Photo Roster?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1098968","Answer":"If the user is not able to print the photo roster, then verify whether the user is using Internet Explorer. Internet Explorer is not compatible with Blackboard and is known to cause issues. If the user is using IE, then recommend to use Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox and try again. For more information, please click on the below mentioned links - <br><br>http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/browsers","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba0","Question":"How do I send an emai or announcementl to students from Blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1099295","Answer":"To send email - <br><br>Under Course Management > Course Tools > Send Email.<br><br>To send announcements - <br><br>1.  Create Announcment link > Create Announcements <br>- OR - <br>2.  Under Course Management > Course Tools > Announcements.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba1","Question":"How so I edit/set content system permissions in Blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1124494","Answer":"1.  Go inside the course > Content System<br>2.  Click on the course id > Hover your mouse over the course content until you see the grey drop down.<br>3.  Click on the drop down > Permissions > Select Specific Users By Place <br>4.  Select Course > Inside courses, select the particular course > Role:Student > Set Permissions: Read and hit submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba2","Question":"How can I add a user from outside UIC to my course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1111166","Answer":"In order for the users to get enrolled in the class they will need a valid UIC net id. Please ask the requestor to send an email to accounts@uic.edu and someone from the team will assist in setting up the user's netids. Once the net id is setup, you can go ahead and add them into your course.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba3","Question":"How can I change the point of entry for my course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1210330","Answer":"1.  Navigate to the course in Blackboard you want to modify.<br>2.  In the Control Panel, click Customization. <br>3.  Click Teaching Style. <br>4.  Under section 2 of the Teaching Style customization page, select your preferred course<br>Entry Point from the drop-down list. Content sections that are NOT available to users will not<br>be listed here. The options will vary depending on what content areas you have established<br>for your course. Typical content areas for course entry point include Announcements or<br>Assignments. <br>5.  Click Submit when finished.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba4","Question":"Where is the BLANK tool in my course? It isn't in the 'Tools' section!","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1204554","Answer":"Tools can be disabled. To enable a tool navigate to the Control Panel > Customization > Tool Availability","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba5","Question":"Why am I am unable to save my responses in an online test?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1182773","Answer":"Use Chrome or Firefox. Delete cookies ( https://kb.iu.edu/d/ahic) . Use a stable wireless connection or switch to wired.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba6","Question":"Why do I see an 'error on convert' message after I tried converting a Collaborate video to mp4?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1186772","Answer":"Contact Blackboard support.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba7","Question":"Why does Echo 360 show a black screen with icon?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1247056","Answer":"Link was copied from address bar. <br>1.  Navigate to the EchoCenter <br>2.  Select the echo <br>3.  Click the \"i\" icon <br>4.  Scroll down to the text box and copy the entire link to embed an iframe or just the address within src=\"...\" to create a hyperlink.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba8","Question":"Can students download or share sharestream videos?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1209207","Answer":"By default students cannot download sharestream videos or see them if they are not registered in the course. These options can be enabled in the ShareStream Media Manager.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342ba9","Question":"Can I copy an Echo from a previous course to my new one?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1234495","Answer":"Either request a copy at lecturecapture@uic.edu <br>- OR - <br>1.  go to echo360.uic.edu <br>2.  Locate the echo <br>3.  Mouse over it and click copy <br>4.  Choose the appropriate options from the drop downs and hit Copy","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342baa","Question":"What does it mean when an Echo360 Section does not exist for my course?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1211967","Answer":"The course is not registered or was not registered properly with the Echo server. Contact lecturecapture@uic.edu","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bab","Question":"Why does Personal Capture say I am not associated with any course?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1201367","Answer":"Your course is not registered with Echo360. Navigate to http://accc.uic.edu/service/lecture-capture and fill out the form to request a new Echo section. This must be done for every course.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bac","Question":"Why is my browser blocking multiple file uploads to blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1200929","Answer":"Security settings prevent the java applet from running. Upload one at a time - or - whitelist UIC's blackboard address under your security settings. This is different for each browser.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bad","Question":"Why can't I add assignments to a weighted column?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1191572","Answer":"This is a known issue that occasionaly pops up. Try switching browsers to another approved browser.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bae","Question":"Can I get a list of guest users on Blacboard Collaborate?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1178732","Answer":"No. You will have to request their information.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342baf","Question":"Can non-UIC students participate in a webinar?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1170479","Answer":"Yes, students can be provided a guest link to a Blackboard Collaborate session. When joining a session you can access a guest URL. Each room also has a link below it allowing you to invite guests.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb0","Question":"Why does it say Error 403: Forbidden when I try to view Echo videos?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1161014","Answer":"#NAME?","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb1","Question":"Why can't I download Echo360 videos?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1137467","Answer":"By default Echo360 videos are not downloadable. Professors can request that videos bet set to downloadable at lecturecapture@uic.edu <br>- OR- <br>1.  navigating to the course/section on the Echo360 server <br>2.  Click edit <br>3.  go to the EchoCenter section <br>4.  check enable video downloads","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb2","Question":"Why does Blacboard collaborate keep dropping me?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1136393","Answer":"It is likely a connection issue. Please use a wired connection or sit closer to the wireless router. Also make sure that your java installation is up to date.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb3","Question":"Why do questions appear to randomized on my test even though I didn't randomize questions?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1144614","Answer":"There are two options for randomizing questions. It is likely the test is set to have randomized answers, which is less obvious. Please try the following:<br>- Click the chevron that appears to the right of the test's title<br>- Select 'Edit the Test'<br>- Click the 'Question Settings' button on the top right<br>- Uncheck the 'Specify random order of answers' found in the 'Display' section at the bottom<br>- Click the 'Submit' button to save settings","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb4","Question":"Why isn't my current class listed in personal capture even though I have registered for it in the past?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1056891","Answer":"The access license is not assigned per person but per class.<br>Therefore you need to request an access for each class you want to use with Echo360.<br>You can make a request to gain access for the class by filling out the form here: https://accc-fs.webhost.uic.edu/uicast/index.cgi <br><br>Make sure to select \"Personal Capture\". <br><br>After completing the request, you will be able to see the course on your Echo360 and you can publish the presentation.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb5","Question":"How do you download Blackboard Collaborate Launcher?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1064429","Answer":"1.  Click \"Tools\", and click \"Blackboard Collaborate\"<br>2.  Join any room.<br>3.  Click \"download the Blackboard Collaborate Launcher.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb6","Question":"How do you upload iSpring files?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1064903","Answer":"Attach the iSpring quickguide","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb7","Question":"How can I caption a video that is intended to be used in a Blacboard course?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1075554","Answer":"http://accessweb.uic.edu/captioning-at-uic/","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb8","Question":"Why can't I launch Blackboard Collaborate?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1068269","Answer":"The solution is to uninstall all the old Java versions. <br><br>1.  Uninstall the old Java from \"Programs and Features\" or \"Add and Remove Programs\" before installing the new version / update.<br>2.  Then download and install both 32-bit and 64-bit Java updates using this link - http://www.java.com/en/download/manual.jsp<br><br>Also, checking your browser might help. If your are using Internet Explorer as your browser, sometimes Java application can't launch the Blackboard Collaborate successfully.<br><br>If this does not work, I also recommend contacting the Blackboard Collaborate support for further support.<br>http://www.blackboard.com/Platforms/Collaborate/Support/Support-for-Blackboard-Collaborate.aspx","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bb9","Question":"How do you delete items in Echo360?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1078232","Answer":"You should be able to delete your items through echo360 website.<br>echo360.uic.edu<br><br>The option to delete the item will be show when you hover over the course you want to get rid of.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bba","Question":"How do you digitize a VHS for in-class use?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1080426","Answer":"You can drop off your VHS at our office. We need a blank DVD with you. <br>As long as the VHS is related to class works, we are able to digitize it.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bbb","Question":"How can I schedule a lecture capture?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1098746","Answer":"Send a lecture capture request from the link below.<br>https://accc-fs.webhost.uic.edu/uicast/index.cgi","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bbc","Question":"Where do we purchase iclicker bases?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1115996","Answer":"Usually you get it from the iClicker representative.<br>Please contact Glen.<br><br>Glen Garrett<br>Show quoted text<br>M: 615.598.3638<br>Glen.Garrett@Macmillan.com","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bbd","Question":"How do you give moderator privileges to someone in Blackboard Collaborate?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1128275","Answer":"In the collaborate session, you can right click the participants and click \"Give moderator privilege,\" and that way you can change the participant's role to a moderator.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bbe","Question":"Where is the Sharestream video my student uploaded?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1148688","Answer":"Go to the student's attemt and try clicking \"Play media\" and click \"Download.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bbf","Question":"Why can't ! upload a powerpoint to BlackboardCollaborate?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1143102","Answer":"Creating the compatible version of the power point is the solution to this problem.<br>To do so, open the power point file and save the same slide from \"Save as.\"<br>Choose \"PowerPoint 97-2003 Presentation.\"<br>Blackboard collaborate should accept this file for upload.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc0","Question":"How do you bulk delete?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1202996","Answer":"Go to Packages and Ulitilies > Bulk delete.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc1","Question":"How can I copy a test from one course to another?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1142406","Answer":"To copy a test from one course to another, please try the following:<br><br>1.  Navigate to Course Management > Course Tools > Tests, Surveys and Pools<br>2.  Choose Tests<br>3.  Find the test you want to copy and mouse over it. You will see a small icon appear with the > symbol. Click it to bring up the context menu.<br>4.  Choose \"Export to local computer\" and save the zip file to your computer where you can find it.<br>5.  Navigate to the Tests section of Tests, Surveys and Pools in the destination course.<br>6.  At the top, click \"Import Test\"<br>7.  Choose \"Browse my Computer\" and find the zip file you downloaded. Click open.<br>8.  Click submit.<br>9.  The test should now be in your Tests, Surveys and Pools, ready to be deployed.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc2","Question":"Can I copy the content from a course that I am not listed as an instructor to my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Course Copy","RT_reference":"1176183","Answer":"In terms of the course copy, only users who were added as \"instructors\" can copy the course content.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc3","Question":"How can I record student attendance in my course site?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1182457","Answer":"Unfortunately, we do not have \"Online Attendance tool\" in Blackboard. <br>To track attendance in Blackboard, some instructors create columns for attendance in Grade Center and manually track the absences.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc4","Question":"How do I export videos out of powerpoint?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1248633","Answer":"- As you are adding narrations to your slides, save the PowerPoint in the .pptx format to save narrate audio<br>- When ready to export, go to File > Export > Create a Video ( help exporting: http://tinyurl.com/hpz88oh) <br>- Upload the exported video to Y","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc5","Question":"How do I get a public link for my sharestream video?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1227554","Answer":"- To retrieve the link for a video, go to: Tools > ShareStream MediaManager > Library > [Name of collection]<br>- To get the link for a video, right-click the video and click 'Show Deeplink/Tiny URL.' Make sure check-box is unchecked so as to avoid authen","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc6","Question":"How do I view corrupted documents submitted through blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1227714","Answer":"Any machine with a valid Microsoft Office installation should be able to open a .doc file as it was the standard used by Microsoft Word until 2003 ( unless the version of Word being used predates 2003) . The new default format is .docx so that should work too.<br><br>Unfortunately, there are many 'corrupt-my-file' programs available online that will corrupt any file that are passed through their system. In such a case, there is no way to tell if the file was actually corrupted ( rare, but possible)  or, corrupted with malicious intent. If this seems like a delay-tactic, you may want to ask your students to submit a PDF file too - it is almost impossible for both files to be corrupted. In this instance, professors may also add the message: \"students are responsible for uploading a readable non corrupt word document\" to future assignments.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc7","Question":"What are my options for recording a guest lecture?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1240586","Answer":"- Blackboard Collaborate, mostly used for live streaming webinars<br>- Echo 360 Lecture Capture, in an equipped classroom<br>- Other, non-UIC: WebX or gotometing","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc8","Question":"How do I fix Audio issues in Collaborate?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1237383","Answer":"During our conversation, you were able to increase the maximum limit for speakers from 3 to 6, as well as test out various microphone/speaker set ups. After trial and error, we still agree that the teleconference offered the best quality, and most consistent sound. In the future, you may try a new headset that connects via USB, but again, the teleconference seemed to work the best for your set up.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bc9","Question":"How can I edit Blackboard notifications?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1235639","Answer":"To edit Blackboard notifications:<br>1.  When you log into Blackboard, click on your name in the top right to open your account menu<br>2.  Click on the alarm clock icon to go to the Updates and Announcements page <br>3.  Then click on the gear in the top right to see a list of notifications to turn on and off <br>4.  Mark the notifications you wish to receive, then click save","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bca","Question":"How long does it take for a Blackboard Collaborate recording to publish?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1212664","Answer":"The expectation for processing recordings should not be that it is immediate. Instead, the recordings are made available afterwards and it may take up to a few hours. There are no known \"peak\" hours for when collaborate is particularly quick or slow.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bcb","Question":"Can I get discussion board notifications via text?","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1217086","Answer":"As for being notified on a discussion thread or forum, your professor would have to allow subscriptions for each forum or thread. Once they do that, you will be able to subscribe to individual forums or threads.<br><br>Blackboard at UIC does not push notifications via text ( SMS) . The Mobile option where your netID is found refers to the Blackboard app, Mobile Learn. If you are using the mobile app, however, there is a known issue with the Mobile Learn in regards to notifications. The notifications through the app do not seem to sync properly to the full site and therefore do not push notifications at all. We apologize for this inconvenience and unfortunately this is not something ITL at UIC can fix though we have brought up requests about it directly to Blackboard.<br><br>While you won't be able to receive notifications through the app or text, you can receive notifications via email.<br><br>You can ask your professor and have them correspond on this email if they would like to allow email subscriptions to the forum, and I can go ahead and make all of the forums available for subscription for them. I would need the course name, and an email from your instructor. Sorry again for the inconvenience, and thank you for your patience.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bcc","Question":"Can I view classroom schedules and when classrooms are being used?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1201419","Answer":"Unfortunately, the ACCC is unable to access this information for you. While we support Blackboard courses, we do not have a list of the physical classroom schedules. For this information, please email your request to Classroom Scheduling which can be reached at: ClassroomScheduling@uic.edu","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bcd","Question":"How can guests view ShareStream videos?","Category":"ShareStream","RT_reference":"1209659","Answer":"Unfortunately, while you can allow guests to view content areas such as the Films to Watch section of your course site, only individuals with netIDs are able to view ShareStream videos. Normally, when an individual is at your site, they are already logged into Blackboard which is why students aren't prompted with a login. Guests, however, will need a login in order to access these videos.<br><br>- Request guest netIDs here: http://accc.uic.edu/service/identity-and-access-management/guest-accounts <br>- Alternatively, you may try to upload these movies to youtube as unlisted for your guests.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bce","Question":"How can I publish a SoftChalk lesson?","Category":"SoftChalk","RT_reference":"1176725","Answer":"https://helpdesk.uic.edu/accc/Ticket/Attachment/14096732/7756726/softchalk_PublishLessons.pdf","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bcf","Question":"How can I send an Echo video to non-UIC faculty for closed-captioning services?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1186946","Answer":"Because Echo normally requires a UIC login, you would complete the following steps to send a video to the DRC faculty without netIDs: <br><br>1.  Log in to Echo 360 at echo360.uic.edu <br>2.  Place your mouse over the desired lecture or video <br>3.  Click \"closed caption\" to download an mp3 file <br>4.  Send the mp3 and accompanying slides to DRC <br><br>The \"closed caption\" option in Echo 360 allows you to download just an mp3 file whereas clicking \"download\" will download the entire Echo 360 folder with many extraneous files -- so be sure to not to choose \"download.\" <br><br>Alternatively, you can download an mp3 ( audio only)  file by clicking \"play mp3\" and then \"download media file.\" Clicking \"play m4v\" will prompt a download of an m4v file ( audio and video) .","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd0","Question":"How can I link to a Blacboard Collaborate recording?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1133108","Answer":"- Find recordings in the Recording Tab from the Collaborate page<br>- Hover over a recording, click the arrow and select \"Add Link\"<br>- Choose a section in your course where you would like to add a link to your recording","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd1","Question":"Can guests participate in Blackboard discussion boards?","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1100971","Answer":"NO, guests will not be able to view or participate in the discussion boards.<br><br>If any of the guests are instructors at UIC, they can be given instructor access to a course for the purposes of participating in Discussion; however, if they are external to UIC, then the only way to give them access would be to create an account by emailing accounts@uic.edu <http://accc.uic.edu/service/identity-and-access-management/guest-accounts>.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd2","Question":"Do videos auto-publish to Echo?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1068150","Answer":"Videos will NOT automatically upload to Blackboard unless you select the \"Auto-Publish\" option prior to recording. This will publish the video to the Recordings area without any edits. Even so, it will not be available to students until you make it available.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd3","Question":"Can students run their own Collaborate sessions?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1070831","Answer":"YES, You can allow students to run a session without the presence of an instructor by selecting the option \"All users join as moderators\" under \"Roles and Access\" when creating the room. This is a common practice for example when creating a study room or group chat as you have described that does not need an assigned facilitator.<br><br>However, students cannot create sessions, so you will have to create the initial session. However, to avoid your having to create a new session every time the student groups want to meet, you can set the \"End Date\" for the session as the end of the semester. Students will still be able to record their sessions every time they log in, and recordings will be published shortly after all users leave the current session. Marking the \"End Date\" as the end of the semester ( ex. Dec 10, 2015)  should allow students to keep using that room for all of their group sessions. Tips: I would recommend that you create a session for each of your groups, ( ex. Group 1, Group 2) . The students can then join the room corresponding to their assigned group number. Note: All students will be able to join ANY room. If you would like to restrict access to just the students in a specific group, you can do this when you create the session under the \"Roles and Access\" options.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd4","Question":"How do you make a course Available to students?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1100947","Answer":"To make courses available to students:<br>Step 1: Go to the course you wish to make available. <br>Step 2: Go to the Control Panel. <br>Step 3: Select Customization. <br>Step 4: Select Properties. <br>Step 5: Select Yes next to \"Make Course Available\". <br>Step 6: Click the blue Submit button.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd5","Question":"Is it possible to access gradebooks from previous courses?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1066761","Answer":"Student grades in courses are not removed/ deleted by Blackboard at any point. They stay in the course as long as an instructor is assigned to that course. Only the instructor on record has access to course resources, including the gradebook. Also grades on Blackboard may not be the official grade. To get official grade information, you can also look up grades posted on Banner. Only faculty have access to Banner to protect the privacy of students and copyright of instructors on Blackboard.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd6","Question":"How do I create assignments on my Blackboard course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Assignments","RT_reference":"1071001","Answer":"To create an assignment in Blackboard:<br>1.  Change Edit Mode to ON and access the course area where you want to create the assignment. <br>On the action bar, point to Assessments to access the drop-down list. ( See attached image)  <br>2.  Select Assignment. <br>3.  On the Create Assignment page, type a Name. Students click this name in the course area to access the assignment. <br>4.  Optionally, in the Assignment Files section, attach a file using Browse My Computer, Browse Course, or Browse Content Collection. <br>5.  Type Points Possible. Optionally, associate a rubric by pointing to Add Rubric to access the drop-down list. <br>6.  Select the check box to Make the Assignment Available. <br>7.  Select the appropriate option for Number of Attempts. <br>8.  For Limit Availability, you can set the assignment to display on a specific date and time and stop displaying on a specific date and time. Select the Display After and Display Until check boxes to enable the date and time selections. Display restrictions do not affect availability, only when the assignment appears. <br>9.  Optionally, select a Due Date. Due dates are used to organize and assign gradable items to grading periods in the Grade Center. If a student submits an assignment after the due date, the submission is identified as late. <br>10.  In the Recipients section, select the All Students Individually option. <br>11.  Click Submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd7","Question":"Is there a way to change the time for online quizzes or tests for one person?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1053907","Answer":"To change the time for online quizzes or tests for one person:<br>1. Enter the desired course site. <br>2. Select the Online Quizzes<br>3. Click the chevron button to the right of the Quiz name ( e.g. Quiz1) .<br>4. Select Edit the Test Options.<br>5. Click Add User or Group.<br>6. Select the user or group the exceptions will be created for.<br>7. Click Submit.<br>8. Select the exceptions. Exceptions can be created for:<br>- Number of attempts<br>- Time of test<br>Note: If a student saves and exits the assessment, the timer continues. For example, if he begins the test on Tuesday, saves and exits it, then completes it on Thursday, his completion time will be 48 hours.<br>- Availability of test using start and end dates<br>- Force completion<br>9.  Click Submit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd8","Question":"How does the student preview option work ?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1145752","Answer":"The student preview user allows you to view the course as a student. When you enter student preview mode, a preview user will be created that will allow you to experience your course as a student. In student preview mode you can:<br>-Submit Assignments<br>-Take Tests<br>-Create blog and discussion posts<br>-Create journal and wiki entries<br>-View student tools such as My Grades<br><br>Once you have activated student preview mode, a thick orange bar will always remain on top, signifying that you are in student preview mode. When you go to exit student preview mode, you will be prompted to either delete the preview user data or to keep it. It is considered best practice to delete any data you created, as any material ( assignments, tests)  you created as a preview user will appear in the course gradebook if the preview user and data is not deleted.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bd9","Question":"Why are my iSpring files not working?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1057757","Answer":"If your iSpring files are not working, it may be because the iSpring files were not initially packaged correctly. If the method you first used to upload your iSpring files in its original Blackboard course site was to upload your iSpring files into the site's content system and then add the 'index.html' file to your content area from there, you may have trouble with the files in a copied course. This method works for the original course site, as all of the iSpring files are uploaded into that site's content system, but if the site is copied into a future site - the 'index.html' file in the future ( copied)  courses would no longer work as all the iSpring files have not been uploaded to the content system, only the 'index.html' file. To fix this, you can follow these steps:<br>1.  Go to one of the original PowerPoint files, click the iSpring tab<br>2.  Click \"Publish\"<br>3.  In the dialog box that appears, ensure that under \"Output Options,\" both 'Desktop ( Flash) ' and 'All in one Flash file' are selected<br>4.  Click Publish. The progress bar that appears should note that your files, including audio, are being processed<br>5.  The final file will appear in Presentation Preview, so you may view the file and confirm that all is as expected<br>6.  Click \"Open Folder\" inside Presentation Preview. This will send you to the location of the files inside your computer<br>7.  The only file you will need for Blackboard is the .swf ( Shockwave Flash Object)  file. The others ( index and data)  can be kept for your records<br>8.  In Blackboard, go to your course and desired content area. Go to Build Content > File and then browse your computer for this newly created .swf file<br>9.  Click Submit<br>This will upload your iSpring presentations so that they will still be usable when copied to future Blackboard course sites. Please note that, using this method, the presentations will not be playable on iPads - they're best viewed on desktop computers and laptops.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bda","Question":"How do you create OR edit a test in Blackboard ?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1172398","Answer":"To create a test in Blackboard:<br>1.  On the Control Panel, expand the Course Tools section and click Tests, Surveys and Pools<br>2.  On the Tests, Surveys and Pools page, click Tests. The Tests page displays all existing tests, and you can also build new tests here.<br>3.  Select Build Test from the dark grey bar<br>4.  Input the following basic information: name of the test, description, instructions. You can use the content editor functions to format the text and include files, images, web links, multimedia and mashups.<br>5.  Click Submit<br><br>After you create a test, you can edit it by:<br>1.  On the Control Panel, expand the Course Tools section and click Tests, Surveys and Pools <br>2.  On the Tests, Surveys and Pools page, click Tests. The Tests page displays all existing tests, here you can select the test you would like to edit.<br>3.  Click on the chevron next to the test you would like to edit, and select edit.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bdb","Question":"How can an Instructor view the safe assign percentage and report for each student submission?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1179986","Answer":"To view SafeAssign reports for individual students:<br>1)  Under your Control Panel, select Grade Center and then select Full Grade Center. If an assignment needs to be graded, a golden circle will appear next to it. <br>2)  Move your mouse over the golden circle, or the already graded assignment you would like to view, and a grey chevron will appear.<br>3)  Click on the chevron and click \"View Attempts\"<br>4)  It will take you to the page where you can view the student's submission and grade them using box on the right.<br>5)  In the same page ( under the grade box) , click on the small arrow near \"Safe Assign\" to view safe assign report and % of match,<br>6)  It will expand now to show you the percentage of match and a link to view the entire report.100% match means everything was copied from some other source.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bdc","Question":"How do you make a Grade center row visible again if it was hidden previously?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1179257","Answer":"To make a row in the Grade Center visible again if it was hidden:<br>1)  Go to Grade Center ->Full grade center<br>2)  Click on the tab \"Manage\" ( On the top above the grade center columns) <br>3)  Click on Row Visibility<br>4)  Click on the check Box against the student or column that is hidden ( will be marked there as hidden)  and click on \"Show Rows\" on top.<br>5)  Hit the submit button","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bdd","Question":"What can be done if copying from Microsoft word to Blackboard does not work properly ?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1224758","Answer":"1)  If you are copying from word into the Blackboard, you can you Ctrl+c - to copy and Ctrl+v to paste. Right click options don't work with blackboard.<br>Refer to this link: https://com.parature.com/link/portal/15026/15028/Article/193/I-can-t-copy-and-paste-in-Blackboard<br><br>2)  You can use the same option as point 1 for Discussion boards. But you also have an alternative, where you can click on the tab \"HTML\" which is present every time people respond to the threads in discussion Board. You can copy paste easily when once you click on this tab. Refer to screenshot 1 to see where it is present.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bde","Question":"How do you edit rubrics and make it available to the students ?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1064869","Answer":"To edit a rubric and make it available to students:<br>1)  Change Edit Mode to ON and point to the plus sign above the course menu. The Add Menu Item drop-down list appears.<br>2)  Select \"Content Area\" from the drop down<br>3)  Type a Name for the link( Say for example.. Rubrics) .<br>4)  Select the Available to Users check box to enable users ( students)  to see the link on the course menu. You can create content ahead of time in your content system, make it unavailable, and then make it available at the appropriate time.<br>5)  Then from there click \"build content\" -> \"file\" -> \"BROWSE CONTENT COLLECTION\" ( if you made a rubric ahead of time and stored it in your content system) <br>6)  From the list of collections, select the ones which you wanted to use it in the course and click Submit.<br>7)  Now all the contents you selected will appear in the course page and student can use i","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bdf","Question":"Are instructors able to use letter grades in Blackboard's Grade Center?","Category":"Blackboard - Grade Center","RT_reference":"1113444","Answer":"In order to use letter grades in Blackboard, you must create a 'Grading Schema.' Grading Schema's calculate a percentage based on students' scores versus the number of points possible. From there, you can create a customized Grading Schema for letter grades, pass/fail or other customized grades. To create a grading schema for your course:<br>1.  In the Grade Center, point to Manage on the action bar and click Grading Schemas<br>2.  On the Grading Schemas page, click Create Grading Schema on the action bar<br>3.  Type a Name. The name appears on the Grading Schemas page and in the drop-down lists for primary disply and secondary display when creating or editing columns in the Grade Center.<br>4.  In the Schema Mapping section, two default rows appear with ranges of percentages. You can edit the two ranges to customize a Pass/Fail schema.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be0","Question":"Is it possible to edit lecture captures in Echo360 after they are recorded?","Category":"Echo360","RT_reference":"1177783","Answer":"It is possible to edit lecture captures by going to the Echo360 website, opening the Echo you would like to edit, and clicking the Edit Media tab at the bottom of the page. Here you will be able to make simple edits to an existing Echo360 recording.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be1","Question":"How does an instructor get a guest link to a Blackboard Collaborate session?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1124523","Answer":"To get a guest link for a Collaborate session:<br>1.  Go to the Blackboard Collaborate link under Course Tools, find the correct room and Edit Room<br>2.  Under Room Attributes on this page, turn the Allow Guests option ON<br>3.  Click Save at the bottom of the page. <br>4.  After that, a new link will appear that says Invite Guests. When you click that link, a small window will pop up that will give you the link for the session. Additionally, when you navigate into the Collaborate Room by clicking on Join Room, the guest link will also be in a grey box on the right-hand side of the screen.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be3","Question":"Is Blackboard Connect a part of the services UIC subscribes to?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1063451","Answer":"No, BlackboardConnect is not a service UIC subscribes to.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342be4","Question":"Why am I unable to talk in Blackboard Collaborate using the iOS app?","Category":"Blackboard - Collaborate","RT_reference":"1223163","Answer":"When using the iOS app to join a collaborate session, you must enable the talk button in order to speak in the session.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bed","Question":"How do I access Lynda.com?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1250096","Answer":"Navigate to go.uic.edu/lynda to be connected directly to the UIC lynda portal","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342bf7","Question":"How can I create an assignment link using SafeAssign?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1066235","Answer":"To create an assignment using SafeAssign, <br>- Log in to your course site.<br>- Click \"Assignment\" menu in the content area.*<br>- Click \"Assignment\" menu and find \"Assessments.\"<br>- Click \"Assignment.\"<br>- Select \"Submission Details.\"<br>- Select \"Check submissions for plagiarism using SafeAssign.\"<br>- Check the box \"Allow students to view SafeAssign originally report for their attempts.\"<br>- Click \"Submit.\"<br><br>For the detailed information, click this link of how to create an assignment menu using SafeAssign: http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/safeassign<br>* Note: if you have not created an assignment menu yet, click \"+\" sign and select Tool link. Type \"Assignments\" and then select \"Assignments.","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b63","Question":"How do you add users to a course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1185261","Answer":"Adding Users to a Blackboard Course SIte:<br>1)  Under 'Control panel', go to 'Users and Groups', then select 'Users'<br>2)  Click on the 'Find Users To Enroll' tab/button<br>3)  Enter the UIC netID ( email id without @uic.edu)  in the Username field<br>4)  Select the role as student or TA or Instructor ( default is Student) <br>5)  Make sure Enrollment Availability is set to Yes<br>6)  Click Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b64","Question":"How do you delete tests from a course site ?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1067926","Answer":"1)  Under Control Panel, Click on Course tools -> Tests, Surveys, and Pools -> Tests. <br>2)  You will have the list of all the tests there and you can delete them one at a time","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b65","Question":"How do you make a link on the content area available to students?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1206939","Answer":"1)  Move the mouse over the folder/content area ( Ex..Course Information)  on the left pane and you will see a chevron appearing.<br>2)  Click on the chevron and hit \"Show Link","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b66","Question":"Where do you find Blackboard help for faculty and students?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1089649","Answer":"Blackboard help for students:<br>1)  Blackboard help for students: https://help.blackboard.com/en-us/Learn/9.1_2014_04/Student<br>2) Search for Blackboard answers: http://help-archives.blackboard.com/Blackboard-Learn/9.1/SP09/EN-US/NAHE/Student/index.htm<br>3)  Video tutorials: https://help.blackboard.com/en-us/Learn/Reference/Blackboard_Learn_Videos/Student_Videos<br><br>Blackboard help for instructors:<br>1) Blackboard help: https://help.blackboard.com/en-us/Learn/9.1_2014_04/Instructor<br>2) Search for Blackboard answers: http://help-archives.blackboard.com/Blackboard-Learn/9.1/SP09/EN-US/NAHE/Instructor/index.htm","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b67","Question":"How do students register their iClicker in Blackboard?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1061548","Answer":"1)  Sign in to Blackboard and access the Blackboard site for<br>the course.<br>2.  Click on the Tools menu button.<br>3.  Click on the \"Register Your i>Clicker Remote ID\"<br>link.<br>4.  Enter your i>Clicker Remote ID in the box and click<br>the Register button ( I>clicker remote id is found on the back of the i>clicker.<br>) <br>Look at the video in the following link in case of any doubts: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zNFzJHB_ubs","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b68","Question":"How do you subscribe to a forum?","Category":"Blackboard - Discussion Board","RT_reference":"1123544","Answer":"1)  Go to Discussion board, you will see the list of forums already created<br>2)  Click on the chevron near the forum name and click edit<br>3)  Click the option \"Allow members to subscribe to forum\" in subscribe option under Forum Settings<br>4)  Click Submit<br><br>This will show the tab \"Subscribe\" to the students, so that they can click on it to subscribe to the forum","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b6d","Question":"How and when can an Instructor remove a question from a test that has already been deployed?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1224653","Answer":"Instructor can delete the question at any point of time. Follow the steps below to do it:<br>1)  Go into the course and into the folder where test is deployed<br>2)  Move your mouse over the test name and you will see a chevron appearing<br>3)  Click on the chevron and hit the option \"Edit the test\" <br>4)  Scroll down to the question you wanted to delete. Near the question, you will see a chevron appearing<br>5)  Click on the chevron and hit \"Delete and Regrade\". This will delete the question from the deployed test and regrade all the students who have already taken the test. For students who have not taken the test, it will just delete the question and they can take the test normally with other questions present","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b70","Question":"What are I spring files, how do you copy them and how do give permissions to students to view them ?","Category":"OTHER","RT_reference":"1150090, 1073682,1108746","Answer":"Follow the steps below to create all-in-one iSpring files and upload them:<br>1.  Go to PowerPoint files, click the iSpring tab<br>2.  Click \"Publish\"<br>3.  In the dialog box that appears, ensure that under \"Output Options,\" both 'Desktop ( Flash) ' and 'All in one Flash file' are selected<br>4.  Click Publish. The progress bar that appears should note that your files, including audio, are being processed<br>5.  The final file will appear in Presentation Preview, so you may view the file and confirm that all is as expected<br>6.  Click \"Open Folder\" inside Presentation Preview. This will send you to the location of the files inside your computer<br>7.  The only file you will need for Blackboard is the .swf ( Shockwave Flash Object)  file. The others ( index and data)  can be kept for your records<br>8.  In Blackboard, go to your course and desired content area. Go to Build Content > File and then browse your computer for this newly created .swf file<br>9.  Click Submit<br><br>For more details: https://helpdesk.uic.edu/accc/Ticket/Attachment/13067164/7227848/Ispring%20File%20Upload.pdf<br><br>For more on giving student permissions to content:<br>https://blackboardhelp.usc.edu/course-content/content-collection/content-collection-file-permissions/","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b76","Question":"How do I add a course menu item to my course?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1079849","Answer":"Go to course site:<br>1)  Hover mouse over '+' ( left corner of page) <br>2)  Select course menu item<br>3)  Type in Name and required info<br>4)  Select availability to students<br>5)  Hit Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7d","Question":"How do I upload a zipped 'Test Bank' into my blackboard course site?","Category":"Blackboard - Tests, Surveys, Pools","RT_reference":"1097232","Answer":"Go to course site and then:<br>1)  Control Panel > Test, Surveys and Pools > Tests > Import Test<br>2)  Browse from computer or content collection<br>3)  Click Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7e","Question":"How can I request to create a Non CRN course site on Blackboard?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"NONE","Answer":"Go to http://accc.uic.edu/service/blackboard/request-site-no-crn<br>Fill in the details<br>Click Submit","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0},{"mongo_id":"576b2d0a963679033b342b7f","Question":"Why can't I see the + sign on the top left of the content area anymore?","Category":"Blackboard - GENERAL","RT_reference":"1111823","Answer":"To see the + icon to add course menu items, \"Edit Mode\" must be on. You can find the Edit Mode toggle switch on the top right hand side of the course site","Status":"Approved","Last_updated_by":"skhan231","Submitted_by":"original","Created_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","Last_updated_on":"2016-05-01T05:00:00.000Z","__v":0}]
